



I am Ancsa Szabo, a UX/UI designer with an administrative background. I am passionate about creating engaging and intuitive digital experiences. My design approach is user-first, and I believe in minimalism, which promotes clarity and usability.

Personal Skills

Visuals

0000

Prototyping O O O

Teamwork





- 07392581236
- ancsa.szabo@sonofabit.ch
- www.linkedin.com/in/mariancsaszabo
- Cemetery Road,Bristol,BS4 3DE

Ancsa Szabo

UX/UI DESIGNER

Education

- **Bath Spa University UX/UI** Design Course September 2024 – Present
- **Click Start course** UX/UI Design, Web Development, **Digital Marketing** August 2024 - September 2024

Work Experience

Self-Taught UX/UI Designer 0

Home, Bristol, 09/2023 - 05/2024

Expert in Figma for wireframes, prototypes, versatile design, and user interfaces.

Data Administrator

RAC, Bristol, 06/2023 - 08/2023

Managed renewal processes, assisted with billing and system migration, and utilized MS Office tools. (Fixed term)

Administrator

Cakesmiths, Bristol, 09/2021 - 11/2022

Processed and managed online orders, handled customer queries, and performed data entry using DPD.